STANDARD FOR LIFE
Here are Mr and Mrs Hans Baksteen -
visitors from Holland who are here in The
Synagogue Church Of All Nations in Lagos Nigeria,
seeking for the fruit of the womb
from God Almighty.
Mr & Mrs Baksteen
This is a document from the Minister of Justice in Holland
registering their application for adoption of a child.
This proves they have given up all hope of having their own child.
But today, they are returning to Jesus Christ, the Giver of life.
You are welcome to The Synagogue Church Of All Nations, in Jesus' name.
Tell us your name and the country you come from.
My name is Josein Baksteen, I'm 31 years old and I'm from Holland.
Who is the man sitting next to you?
The man sitting next to me is my husband.
And the problem that brought me to the Synagogue
is the problem of looking for the fruit of the womb.
I went twice through some surgery and
they did some research.
They found out that there was a problem but were unable to specify what the problem was.
There was a problem which did not allow me to conceive.
My husband is having a problem of low sperm count.
That is why the combination of our problems makes it very difficult for us to have a baby.
This is my second visit and on the first visit, I discussed it with the prophet.
I told him that we were in the process of adopting, which had taken three years.
He advised me not to continue with the adoption and to bring my husband,
that we would have our own baby.
Let's hear from your husband.
My name is Hans Baksteen.
The woman beside me is my wife.
I'm in The SCOAN today because we are in need of the fruit of the womb.
My wife went to several hospitals and had some surgeries
in an attempt to fall pregnant but found no solution.
When we found out that there was no medical solution,
then we started the process of adoption.
Here you can see the permission given to adopt a baby from the Ministry of Justice.
It is an official permit to adopt a baby from another country.
We were intending to adopt a child from Ethiopia.
Is this why you came here today?
This is why I'm here because I believe that God is able to solve this problem for us
and that He can give us a baby.
HEALING TIME
This is the emergency section of The SCOAN
where visitors from all over the world have come
to receive a touch from our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ
through His able servant Prophet T.B. Joshua.
Among them are Mr and Mrs Baksteen.
Be healed, in Jesus' name.
Here is Prophet T.B. Joshua stretching forth this hand
to command out everything that is not of Jesus,
and to replace it with what is of Jesus.
It is God's desire for everyone to be restored to full and abundant life.
Jesus Christ is now shaking the obstacle of the problem they have faced for so long.
Lord I believe
In Your holy name
You are free today, in the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Time with Jesus is time with joy
as Prophet T.B. Joshua assures them that their blessing is not far from them.
They now have something to shout "Hallelujah!" about.
A few months later, Mr and Mrs Baksteen came back to The SCOAN
to testify that Mrs Baksteen is now pregnant.
To God be the Glory!
TESTIMONY TIME
Jesus Christ says what He means and He means what He says.
When He says you are blessed, you are blessed indeed.
Hans and Josein have come singing and dancing back into The Synagogue,
showing the blessing of God in their lives.
Our names are Mr and Mrs Hans and Josein Baksteen.
We are from Holland and the problem that brought us to The SCOAN
was low sperm count and fruit of the womb.
We came to Nigeria and last March Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for us.
Then we went back to Holland and we met as husband and wife.
And after that my wife became pregnant
Now, you can see her - she is seven and a half months pregnant.
Praise the Lord for that!
Our advice to all people who are looking for the fruit of the womb is:
Trust in the Lord and be patient and what He did for us, He can also do for you.
Praise the Lord!
My name is Josein Baksteen.
I'm all the way from Holland.
And as you can see I'm pregnant now.
Here I am standing in front of you for the glory of God,
telling you that I'm pregnant and I'm very very happy.
Testimony Time
A few months later, Mr And Mrs Hans Baksteen came back to The SCOAN
with their bouncing baby to testify to the goodness of God in their lives.
Mr & Mrs Baksteen Arriving At The SCOAN With Their Baby
Mr and Mrs Baksteen are back to The SCOAN with their child
which is definitely something to be happy about.
Glory be to God, they have received from Jesus Christ.
Mr & Mrs Baksteen Arriving At The SCOAN With Their Baby
Mr and Mrs Hans Baksteen, the blessed parents, are now walking
in the midst of the people of God with their newborn baby
to testify that God knows every need you face and He is ready to supply them.
So, just believe!
Mr & Mrs Baksteen
Enter The SCOAN Rejoicing
They Sit In The Midst Of Other Mothers Blessed With Miracle Babies
My name is Josein Baksteen.
I'm from Holland.
My baby's name is Promise Baksteen.
The man sitting next to me is my husband Hans Baksteen.
When I came to The SCOAN, I was very surprised seeing all these miracle babies.
I wasn't even thinking about having another baby anymore
because we had waited for such a long time.
I became very happy because I thought if God can do this for these people,
He can surely do it for us.
We were in the process of adopting a baby which is a very long process.
It takes five years to adopt a baby and we were in this process for three years.
We had all the official papers ready.
The Prophet prayed over the problems of fruit of the womb and low sperm count.
He prayed over our problems and we went back home.
We met as husband and wife and after a while, I became pregnant.
Praise the Lord!
While I was seven months pregnant, I visited The SCOAN.
The prophet said, "You will deliver a baby girl and her name will be Promise."
That was a real promise of God.
As you can see, we have a bouncing baby girl.
Her name is Promise, and we are very very happy.
Praise the Lord!
We thank the Lord for what He has done in our lives.
He is good, He is so good.
My name is Hans Baksteen.
I'm the husband of Josein who is sitting beside me.
The name of the baby is Promise Joy Illeri Oluwa.
Mr & Mrs Baksteen With Their Baby Promise
Her name means "Promise of God".
The problem that brought us to The SCOAN was the problem of barrenness.
The problem on my part was low sperm count.
Last year March, I was invited to come with my wife to The SCOAN.
The man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, prayed over our problems.
After that, we went home and met as husband and wife.
My wife got pregnant.
After nine months, she delivered a beautiful bouncing
baby girl named Promise of God.
We thank God for what He has done in our lives.
Our advice to couples who are also looking for the fruit of the womb
is to trust God because He can also do for you what He has done for us.
Mr & Mrs Baksteen With Their Baby Promise
Baby Promise Crawling At The SCOAN
Baby Promise, Now Walking,
Returns To The SCOAN
This is Promise Baksteen.
She's growing stronger day by day and is now walking.
Promise is very happy to be back in The SCOAN today.
She has come with her parents to give God all the glory.
Baby Promise, Now Walking,
Returns To The SCOAN
TT: Lizz Ndungu ,02:01:2018
RV:Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 30/06/2018 + Mel